One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I grabbed hold, digging in my claws
te ni totte tsume o tateta
but the future
sono mirai wa
blurred together, colors running
nijimu iro ni kasunde mieta
A red that can swallow even summer's hues
natsu no iro mo nuritsubusu you na aka ni
bokura no koe kakikesareteiku you de
now attempts to blot out our voices
Move those halting feet of yours
tachidomaru sono ashi o fumidasou ze
Don't let stand the lies for show
misekake no uso yarisugosu yori
I'll give up countless mornings for my vows
nandome no asa chikai to hikikaeru yo
For the dream that we shared
bokura ga miteita yume
What in the world is that?
What incredible Haki!
We’d better get out of here, fast!
Zoro! This fight is over, let’s go!
He ain’t gone down yet...
Jinbe!
Sanji?!
You have that idiot yet?
Handling it now!
We’re going, Zoro!
Call it a win for you!
Sorry, Rob Lucci...
Fishman Karate:
Five Thousand Brick...
...Chop!
Cipher Pol “Aigis” Zero...
Rob Lucci.
Where is York?
We’ve got to hurry!
Hey...
What the hell is that?!
York is still being held captive in the control room
on the fourth floor of Building A.
The two who just fled from here...
...were Roronoa Zoro
and First Son of the Sea Jinbe.
And five of the Straw Hats,
along with two of the Vegapunks,
are preparing to escape
at the rear entrance of the Labophase.
There are also 85 Cipher Pol agents...
...and four Seraphim
in the basement of the lab.
Vegapunk’s broadcast resumes
in six minutes.
Well done.
I have no further questions for you.
One more thing...!
My partner’s seriously injured,
he should still be in the control room...
Please, spare him!
That will prove difficult...
One does not attempt to step on insects...
It simply happens.
You’re as...
...strong as ever,
you big ol’ Giants, you!
Straw Hat!
I hardly recognized ya!
How do you know the appearance of
Elbaf’s god of legend?!
Your outfit pleases us greatly!
I dunno whatcha mean by that,
but let’s catch up later!
The Giants!
A most unpleasant combination!
Those are some humongous beasts!
Just like the savage beasts
in the forests of Elbaf!
Hey, big guy!
We don’t wanna fight ‘em!
We gotta get outta here!
Oh, we know!
We just ran into Sanji!
Hueh?!
He said, “If you see Luffy,
tell him to run around the back of the island”!
Dorry, Brogy! Counting on you two!
You got it!
We’ll see you later!
We read about you in the newspaper
and came to help you all escape!
It said you were surrounded
by the Navy!
Zoro &
Jinbe
Luffy & Giants
Current location
Elbaf ship
Sanji &
Vegapunk
Bonney
and the rest
Nami, Usopp
Egghead,
surrounded by the Navy...
This is how the Straw Hats
are currently scattered about.
Elbaf ship
Bonney
and the rest
Luffy & Giants
Current location
Nami, Usopp
and the rest
Sanji &
Vegapunk
Zoro &
Jinbe
Elbaf ship
Bonney
and the rest
Luffy & Giants
Current location
Let’s head back to the ship, then!
Sanji &
Vegapunk
We’d better let everyone know!
Looks like the Bosses
met up with Straw Hat!
Back to the ship!
Prepare to withdraw!
Aye!
We should just make
our way back with them!
We could plunder their battleships,
but we won’t find treasure aboard!
You ain’t wrong!
Dammit!
Is that their signal to escape?
That presents a problem.
I must sound a warning of my own, then...
A warning not to escape!
The island’s pulsing again!
Hey!
Whaaaa?!
Sun-Shield
Man, that freaked me out...
Almost lost ‘em!
There.
You okay, Straw Hat?!
Got all your bits ‘n pieces back?
Yeah, thanks!
You’ve got quite the
hilarious body now!
And you look
stronger than ever, to boot!
Ya think so?
Anyway...
Yeah...
That Conqueror’s roar...
Who’s he supposed to be?
Some uppity World Government guy!
Brogy!
Yeah!
Svalinn Sun-Shield!
We have much to settle with your kind...
Do you not understand
the likes of who he is?!
Yeah!
Of course we do!
He’s our friend!
Skilja Split!
Your friend?
Nonsense.
I care not for the relationships
of insects that band together...
And before you call him something else,
he must be crushed!
Removed from the historical record...
...for good!
Those’re totally poisonous!
Don’t touch ‘em!
Charge!
How d’ya like a taste of
yer own poison?!
What?! They exploded!
Bosses!
The fire’s gonna block off the forest!
Right, let’s get moving!
You blew ‘em to bits!
Better hurry, better hurry!
They’re unkillable, after all!
What do you mean, “unkillable”?
How should I know?! No matter
what we do, they just keep comin’ back!
I’ve never heard of that kind of power,
or of any race that has it!
Best get runnin’, then!
Run!
All right, we’re almost there!
We’d be there faster
if you’d help, dammit!
Hurry up, Jinbe, Zoro!
I hear you, we’ll be right there!
It’s faster to just run!
Hey, look at that!
In front of the ship!
You won’t be boarding this ship,
Jewelry Bonney!
There’s that real bad feeling...
Let... me... oooout!
Uh?
It’s a monsteeeer!
Where is the room on the monitor?
It talked!
Who’re you?!
Just go awaaaay!
Kizaru, sir!
You must let us treat you!
Show us your wounds!
I certainly have a wound...
And it runs deep...
Then we need to act fast!
Where are you hurt?!
Just let me rest...
Joyboy...
Northwest coast of Egghead,
reporting in!
Something far larger than the Giants
has appeared on the island!
The fire isn’t affecting it at all!
The giant creature
standing in the fire...
...seems to be groaning
about something...
Sorry...
Sorry, Joyboy...
All Pacifista Mk. IIIs have been incapacitated!
I want more pressure on Egghead!
More shells!
You will not let Emperor
Straw Hat’s crew escape!
You will not let Jewelry Bonney get away!
A mere twelve-year-old girl...
...and you gave her the power
to destroy an entire country?
A foolish way to go about
committing treason, Vegapunk!
Hurry, back to the ship!
Some insanely tough guys
just came ashore!
Don’t let them sail out!
Sink the Elbaf ship!
Make for the northeast shore!
This is far as you criminals go!
Max Power!
Damn roadblock!
You will not pass!
Outta the way!
Strong...
Steam...
...Right!
...Knuc—oobph!
Jewelry Bonney!
Brace yourself!
Look after my Daddy, Giant!
Sure! He’s in good hands!
Jewelry Bonney, you snot-nosed brat!
I’m not gonna let you have
those weapons!
Don’t call my father a weapon!
Cra—
D-Don’t...!
My Daddy is a hero,
you big-chinned old fart!
Take it back!
Stop it! This just looks wrong!
Labophase
I can’t help but notice
you’re not drinking your Vega Coffee.
It was too hot!
I’ve got a sensitive tongue, you know!
That’s mean of you, Shaka.
You know he can’t handle hot things...
Four minutes to go, Stella.
Oh, yes, right.
Yeowhot!
Are you certain that it is this room?
I’m pretty sure this’s where
they were recording...
Uh?
Uweh?!
Hold on!
Wait, wait! Don’t do anythin’ crazy!
Stella, there is not much time...
See? You didn’t stop a thing!
Using a thermoelectric element,
if we cool down the coffee
by converting heat energy...
Even I’d hide the Transponder Snail
sendin’ out the signal somewhere else, if I was Stella!
Then I shall simply destroy the entire lab.
Not an option!
The second floor of Building B’s for weapons development.
And the first floor is a power plant.
The third floor of Building C’s...
...where we keep rows of
high-pressure gas cylinders.
If any of ‘em are destroyed,
it’ll set off everything in the lab,
and the lab’ll go boom
along with Punk Records!
If that is so, then ponder!
You, too, ought to share
his neural pathways!
Of course I’m gonna stop this
big, dumb broadcast.
If they keep committin’ crimes,
it makes it that much harder for me to get in with yous.
Whatsa matter?
I sense the voice of a small creature.
In Punk Records?
Oh! Could it be a Transponder Snail?
The Transmission Transponder Snail
was cooked up just recently.
It’s got a cone-like spiral shell, like this.
You will guide me to the entrance.
Good for you.
Looks like you were beneath his notice.
Both of us were.
Still, what was that monster?
Judging from the conversation,
one of the Five Elders, I’d reckon.
Thought as much.
Pretty off-putting transformation he’s got.
Did they abandon you, Stussy?
After you took the trouble to
stab us in the back, poor thing...
I hate to disappoint you,
but I chose to stay here.
Someone has to carry out
the final mission.
What?!
Then we’re leaving Stussy behind?!
Ain’t nothin’ doin’ ‘bout it!
Da barrier’s gotta go down da moment da ship can get out!
Da Frontier Dome can only be deactivated
from da control room.
She volunteered!
Ain’t thankin’ her and den us gettin’ out
da best way to repay her?
You bet I’m going to put everything I’ve got into running away, but...
Robin...
We might lower the barrier,
all thanks to her,
but we aren’t capable of flying as far as
Vegaforce-01 was supposed to carry us...
Dat’s right, Nico Robin.
Ah mathed it out.
Based on basic physics,
dis ship’s definitely
gonna to fall to da ground!
Whaaaa?!
Whaaaah?!
Hey, the Coup De Burst is ready for use!
Once Zoro and Jinbe get here,
we’ll make a super jump towards the sea!
We’ve got a big problem!
We need more than just the Coup De Burst
to reach the sea!
Whaaaa?!
If it looks like we won’t be able to reach the sea,
then I know your strength’ll carry us through!
Must be hard bein’ your ship!
But Ah like dat can-do attitude!
It’s always dat kind o’ strength
dat makes miracles!
And dat’s comin’ from a scientist!
Ah’ll make sure yer ship
lands on da water safely!
Trust me!
Edison!
Doooon’t!
Y’all absolutely gotta make it outta here,
Straw Hats!
Simulated external damage: 78 percent.
Not enough ta kill me! Let’s go!
Edison!
There's an inward wind...
pulling us toward the island!
This is some crazy suction!
Goin’ forward ain’t happening!
Ya big jerk!
If yer that hungry,
chow down on some buildings!
That’s the stuff!
Aw, crud...
Losing... my... strength...
That was a good one!
I’m pooped...
Whaaaa?!
What’s happened to you, Straw Hat?!
You’ve turned into some old stranger!
All... outta... food power...
Food? You want some Hákarl?
Hákarl?
This.
What’s this smell?
It’s fermented shark.
Elbaf’s emergency rations!
Eat up, now!
It’s good once you get used to it.
Oh, yeah!
Smelled nasty, but my energy’s back!
Your body works in simple ways!
Now you’re back to your old self!
Look out! The boar’s coming!
Chew on this!
Gear 3:
Gum-Gum...
...Red...
...Roc!
Yowwww!
How freakin’ hard is your body?!
Whoa, hey, yo!
What’s that, what’s that?!
Something’s down there!
Huh?! A crab?!
Stella, one minute to go.
You don’t have to tell me!
This must be it...
Your luck has run out, Vegapunk.
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop beep-beep-beep-bup-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipii pipopii, pipopiipii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep
Piipapii papipo, piipapii
No No No No No norenai
No, no, no, no, no, not feelin' it
kobiritsuichatte mou odorenai
I'm all stiff, all outta dances
My head feels so good, 'f I get unlucky again
atama Feel so good, mata Unlucky demo
Cola de fukitobase yowaki o
just gonna blow away the shy with a cola
Hey all you boys & girls! Looking good!
soko no Boys & Girls! omae ii yatsu
Hey all you boys & girls!
soko no Boys & Girls!
Update failed. I've had enough!
appudeto wa shippai kori gori
Wasn't it OK 'til yesterday?
kinou made nara seikai?
La la la la la la, run, run, run...
ran ran ran ran ran ran Run Run Run
"Hiding yet?"
mou ii kai?
You ready yet, up for a dance
junbi wa douyo odoreru no?
bukkowareteru kono jidai
in this broken era?
"Come find us!"
mou ii yo!
Spread out from here, drop into the world
koko kara kakusan sekai e Drop
Let loose on the stage of freedom and liberation
jiyuu to kaihou no Stage e
Those rising heads're punks!!!!!! No way!!!
wakiagaru atama ga Punk!!!!!! No way!!!
Sick of waitin', goof off and dance
matenaiyo fuzaketa Dance
Dopamine spilling over
afuredasu dopamin
The lonely singing in unity
kodoku ga tsudoi utau koushin
Bip-bip-bip-bup-bup-bup-bup-bupping
pipipi papapapapatteru
Can't can't can't count me out yet
mada mada mada horobinai
There's some stranger waving me over
shiranai dareka ga temaneki da
Smilin' so wide that it can't be real
uso mitai ni waratteru